plexusworldwide.com 2015-06-07

# Plexus - Privacy

Plexus Worldwide Inc. respects your individual privacy. This Privacy Policy documents our adherence to the highest industry standards for the protection of your personal information. By visiting this web site ("Site") or using any of the services offered on the Site, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective as of October 1, 2011, applies to information collected through the Site and covers the following areas:

  * What personally identifiable information is collected by Plexus through the Site;
  * How Plexus uses this information;
  * With whom Plexus may share this information;
  * What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control; and How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

##### 1\. Information Collection and Use

Plexus collects information on the Site at two different stages. First, we collect anonymous, aggregate information (such as domain name or IP address) from all visitors to the Site. This type of information is never linked to any personally identifiable information and is only used in the aggregate to generate statistical reports about the use of the Site. Second, we require the submission of certain personally identifiable information when you use the services available on the Site. For example, your use of your username and password allows us to identify you as a distributor of Plexus products.

##### 2\. Personal Information of Children Under 13

Plexus complies with the requirements of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA") and the FTC's rule interpreting COPPA (16 CFR Â§ 512). This Site is not directed to children and we do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age through this Site.

##### 3\. Use of Your Personal Information

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, Plexus does not sell, rent, or share user information to or with any third party not affiliated with or owned by Plexus, except service providers who may assist Plexus in areas such as data storage. Plexus will never give or sell your personal information to be used for the purposes of sending you unsolicited commercial offers (such as spam) from any third party. We will not ourselves use your personal information to send you unsolicited commercial offers. However, we may need to contact you for purposes other than marketing, as for example regarding the status of the Site, your account or other matters related to your role as a distributor of Plexus products. You may not opt-out of these kinds of communications.

##### 4\. Use of Aggregate Information

We store information that we collect through log files to create a profile of our users. Log files record internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. A profile is stored information detailing how individual users use the Site. It is used solely for internal purposes, to help us improve the experience of our users. We do not share your profile with any third parties.

##### 5\. Disclosure of Personal Information As Required By Law

We will disclose personal information when required by law, or if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on us, (b) protect and defend our rights, or (c) protect the rights, property, and other interests of our users or others.

##### 6\. Security

Plexus takes commercially reasonable precautions to protect your information. However, given the nature of the Internet and the fact that network security measures are not infallible, we cannot guarantee the security of your information. We also make an effort to protect your information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers that store your personally identifiable information are housed in a secure environment. When registering for access to a secure area of the Site, we will ask you to select a username and password. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also, remember to sign out of the registered site and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence when accessing your computer. If you have any questions about the security at our Site, you can send a message to the webmaster at [webmaster@plexusworldwide.com](mailto:webmaster@plexusworldwide.com)

##### 7\. Correcting, Updating, Deleting and Deactivating Personal Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, you may contact us to correct, update or delete and deactivate our record of your personally identifiable information.

##### 8\. Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will prominently post a notice on the main page and other pages to alert you of the change. If the Privacy Policy changes materially so that your personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will try to contact you by e-mail to give you a choice as to whether or not we may use your information in this different manner. However, you are responsible for ensuring we have a current working e-mail address for you. If the e-mail address you have given us is incorrect or no longer operable, we will have no further obligation to notify you apart from posting the notice on our Site. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on the main page notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.

##### 9\. Contact Information

For further information about this site or Plexus products, please contact us.
